(Raj:)But your ideas are stupid
and I want a Jet Ski.
(Sheldon:)I found it. The ring is mine.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand why in this group
I never get my way.
(Leonard:)You always get your way.
(Sheldon:)I'll stipulate to that
if you give me the ring.
Hey. Enjoying your food
that I actually brought you...
(Penny:)...instead of promising food
but bringing you a box of random crap?
(Leonard:)Yeah, it's delicious.
The sarcasm's a little stale, though.
[HOWARD LAUGHS]
(Leonard:)How about this? Until we figure out
what to do with the ring, Penny holds it.
(Penny:)-What ring?
-This ring.
(Sheldon:)Looking for something?
-Will you hold this for a couple of days?
-Why?
(Leonard:)It's a prop from a movie
and we're kind of fighting over it.
The first piece of jewelry
my boyfriend gives me...
(Penny:)...is a prop from a movie
and I don't even get to keep it?
If you had gone out with me years ago...
...you'd have my Aunt Ida's brooch...